Eleanor Dickinson collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series IV: Moving image items
  - AFC 1970/001: MV036, July 15, 1977, 1 videoreel (32 min., 20 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Rev. Joe Turner, #1; Camp Creek, West Virginia. Original ID # V-77-E-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV037, July 15, 1977, 1 videoreel (32 min., 20 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Brother Joe Turner, #2; Camp Creek, West Virginia. Original ID # V-77-E-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV038, July 15, 1977, 1 videoreel (32 min., 40 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Rev. Joe Turner, #3; Holiness. Original ID # V-77-E-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV039, July 15, 1977, 1 videoreel (32 min., 19 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Brother Joe Turner #4; Rev. Pappy Beaver. Original ID # V-77-E-4.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV040, July 16, 1977, 1 videoreel (32 min., 15 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Rev. Bob Elkins, #1. Original ID # V-77-F-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV041, July 16, 1977, 1 videoreel (32 min., 14 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Rev. Bob Elkins, #2. Original ID # V-77-F-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV042, July 16, 1977, 1 videoreel (32 min., 24 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Rev. Bob Elkins, #3. Original ID # V-77-F-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV043, July 20, 1977, 1 videoreel (33 min., 2 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Brother Paul Breeden, #1. Original ID # V-77-G-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV044, July 20, 1977, 1 videoreel (32 min., 53 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Brother Paul Breeden, #2. Original ID # V-77-G-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV045, July 22, 1977, 1 videoreel (32 min., 50 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Brother Breeden's Apostolic Church #3; Revival - Rev. Manifred Polk, Cathedral of Deliverance. Original ID # V-77-H-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV046, 1977, 1 videoreel (32 min., 11 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Brother H.H. Mayes - photos. Original ID # V-77-I-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV047, 1977, 1 videoreel (32 min., 15 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Pappy Beaver's Revival, #2. Original ID # V-77-J-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV048, 1 videoreel (19 min., 30 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Epilogue "Brother Mayes" (edited master). Original ID # V-77-K-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV049, 1 videoreel (32 min., 41 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Epilogue "Brother Mayes" (third generation copy). Original ID # V-77-L-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV050, 1 videoreel (21 min., 53 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Brother H.H. Mayes, #1. Original ID # V-77-M-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV051, 1 videoreel (25 min., 2 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Brother H.H. Mayes, #2. No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV052, 1 videoreel (helical) (32 min., 52 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Greater Gesthemane Church of God in Christ, #1. Original ID # V-78-A-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV053, 1 videoreel (31 min., 14 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Greater Gesthemane Church of God in Christ, #2. Original ID # V-78-A-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV054, 1 videoreel (ca. 32 min.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Greater Gesthemane Church of God in Christ, #3. Original ID # V-78-A-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV055, 1 videoreel (ca. 32 min.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Greater Gesthemane Church of God in Christ, #4. Original ID # V-78-A-4.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV056, 1 videoreel (32 min., 53 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Homecoming, #1. Original ID # V-78-B-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV057, 1 videoreel (33 min., 2 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Homecoming, #2. Original ID # V-78-B-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV058, 1 videoreel (32 min., 24 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Homecoming, #3. Original ID # V-78-B-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV059, 1 videoreel (32 min., 14 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Homecoming, #4. Original ID # V-78-B-4.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV060, 1 videoreel (22 min., 6 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Homecoming, #5. Original ID # V-78-B-5.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV061, 1 videoreel (30 min., 21 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Orville Sisk, 74 years. Original ID # V-78-C-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV062, 1 videoreel (32 min., 21 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Schilling--Songs; Revival--Denton #1. Original ID # V-78-D-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV063, 1 videoreel (32 min., 24 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Revival--Denton, #2. Original ID # V-78-E-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV064, 1 videoreel (31 min., 50 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Revival--Denton, #3. Original ID # V-78-E-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV065, 1 videoreel (27 min., 26 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Revival--Denton, #4. Original ID # V-78-E-4.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV066, June 23, 1978, 1 videoreel (32 min., 12 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Camp Creek, #1. Original ID # V-78-F-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV067, June 23, 1978, 1 videoreel (32 min., 11 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in.(width)
    Camp Creek, #2. Original ID # V-78-F-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV068, June 23, 1978, 1 videoreel (32 min., 33 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Camp Creek, #3. Original ID # V-78-F-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV069, June 24, 1978, 1 videoreel (32 min., 40 sec.): analog, sound (quadrophonic), black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Jolo, West Virginia, #1. Original ID # V-78-G-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV070, June 24, 1978, 1 videoreel (32 min., 40 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Jolo, West Virginia, #2. Original ID # V-78-G-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV071, June 24, 1978, 1 videoreel (32 min., 20 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Jolo, West Virginia, #3. Original ID # V-78-G-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV072, June 24, 1978, 1 videoreel (33 min., 32 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Jolo, West Virginia, #4. Original ID # V-78-G-4.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV073, June 24, 1978, 1 videoreel (32 min., 54 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    #5 Jolo, West Virginia 6-24-78. Original ID # V-78-G-5.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV074, June 25, 1978, 1 videoreel (32 min., 34 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Camp Creek, #1. This tape documents Eleanor Dickinson attacked by preacher's daughters. Original ID # V-78-H-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV075, June 25, 1978, 1 videoreel (32 min., 40 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Camp Creek, #2. Original ID # V-78-H-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV076, June 25, 1978, 1 videoreel (32 min., 28 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Camp Creek, #3. Original ID # V-78-H-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV077, June 25, 1978, 1 videoreel (32 min., 21 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Camp Creek, #4; Turner, #1. Original ID # V-78-H-4.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV078, June 26, 1978, 1 videoreel (32 min., 22 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Turner, #2. Original ID # V-78-I-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV079, 1978, 1 videoreel (32 min., 50 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Brother H.H. Mayes. The recording was made on the 28th of an unknown month, in 1978. Original ID # V-78-J-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV080, July 2, 1978, 1 videoreel (29 min., 18 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Holders Grove, #1. Original ID # V-78-K-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV081, 1 videoreel (32 min., 34 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Holders Grove, #2; then Jeffords. Original ID # V-78-K-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV082, 1 videoreel (33 min., 44 sec.): analog, sound, color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Beaver Lord's Supper, #1. Original ID # V-78-L-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV083, 1 videoreel (30 min., 13 sec.): analog, sound, color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Beaver Lord's Supper, #2. Original ID # V-78-L-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV084, 1 videoreel (33 min., 40 sec.): analog, sound, color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Beaver, #3. Original ID # V-78-L-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV085, 1 videoreel (31 min., 28 sec.): analog, sound, color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Beaver, #4; Creek baptism, #1. Original ID # V-78-L-4.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV086, 1 videoreel (32 min., 24 sec.): analog, sound, 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Creek baptism. Original ID # V-78-M-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV087, 1 videoreel (35 min., 20 sec.): analog, sound, color (bar); 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Creek baptism, #3. Original ID # V-78-M-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV088, 1 videoreel (28 min., 28 sec.): analog, sound, color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Creek baptism, #4; Tent Revival. Original ID # V-78-M-4.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV089, 1 videoreel (32 min., 25 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Rev. Love, #1. Original ID # V-78-N-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV090, 1 videoreel (28 min., 22 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Rev. Love, #2. Original ID # V-78-N-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV091, 1 videoreel (29 min., 20 sec.): analog, 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Rev. Love, #3. Original ID # V-78-N-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV092, 1 videoreel (32 min., 40 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Int. "Revival!" Tony T. Original ID # V-79-A-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV093, March 4, 1979, March 11, 1979, 1 videoreel (28 min., 45 sec.): 7 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV094, March 11, 1979, 1 videoreel (37 min., 11 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Greater Gesthemane Church of God in Christ, #2. Original ID # V-79-B-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV095, 1 videoreel (27 min., 45 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Greater Gesthemane Church of God in Christ. Original ID # V-79-B-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV096, 1 videoreel (65 min., 15 sec.): 7 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    New Light Missionary Baptist Church, #1 and #2 (original). No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV097, 1 videoreel (27 min., 36 sec.): 7 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    New Light Missionary Baptist Church, #3 (original). No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV098, April 1, 1979, 1 videoreel (65 min., 30 sec.): 7 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Cloretta. No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV099, 1 videoreel (63 min., 2 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 7 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    New Light Missionary Baptist Church, #1. Original ID # V-79-C-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV100, 1 videoreel (0 min.): analog, sound only (no image); 7 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Beaver, #1; Beaver, #2. Original ID # V-79-C-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV101, 1 videoreel (64 min., 54 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 7 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Faith Deliverance Temple, #1. Original ID # V-79-D-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV102, 1 videoreel (63 min., 13 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 7 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Faith Deliverance Temple, #2. Original ID # V-79-D-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV103, 1 videoreel (32 min., 16 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    New Light Missionary Baptist Church, #1. Original ID # V-79-E-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV104, 1 videoreel (0 min.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    New Light Missionary Baptist Church, #2. Original ID # V-79-E-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV105, 1 videoreel (32 min., 46 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Apostolic Faith Church. Original ID # V-79-F-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV106, 1979, 1 videoreel (67 min., 14 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Revivals. Original ID # V-79-G-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV107, August 4, 1979, 1 videoreel (31 min., 14 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Holiness Church of Jesus Christ. Original ID # V-79-H-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV108, August 4, 1979, 1 videoreel (31 min., 14 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Holiness Church of Jesus Christ. Original ID # V-79-H-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV109, August 5, 1979, 1 videoreel (32 min., 14 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Holiness Church of Jesus Christ. Original ID # V-79-I-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV110, August 8, 1979, 1 videoreel (32 min., 43 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Sister Lillie, Brother H.H. Mayes and tent scenes. Original ID # V-79-I-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV111, 1 videoreel (32 min., 45 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Sister Lillie Mayes, Brother H.H. Mayes. Original ID # V-79-J-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV112, 1 videoreel (32 min., 44 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Uncle Lem Owenby; J.T. Higdon. Original ID # V-79-K-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV113, 1 videoreel (30 min., 6 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Pentecostal revival meetings in California. No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV114, 1 videoreel (93 min., 5 sec.): 7 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Revival photographs, #1; Brother H.H. Mayes, #2; signs. No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV115, 1 videoreel (32 min., 8 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Mrs. Irene Russell and car, 1/1. Original ID # V-80-A-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV116, July 7-9, 1980, 1 videoreel (helical) (31 min., 8 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Roadside signs, revival tents, #2. Original ID # V-80-B-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV117, 1 videoreel (32 min., 17 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Interview - preacher; tent revival; Int., 3/2. Original ID # V-80-C-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV118, July 11, 1980, 1 videoreel (31 min., 55 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Camp Creek Church of Jesus Christ, #4. Original ID # V-80-D-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV119, 1 videoreel (30 min., 15 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Danny and Darlene Turner; Jesus Church, 5/1. Original ID # V-80-E-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV120, July 13, 1980, 1 videoreel (31 min., 55 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Micco West Virginia, 6/2. Original ID # V-80-E-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV121, 1 videoreel (32 min., 51 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Country music; tent revival, 7/1. Original ID # V-80-G-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV122, July 17, 1980, 1 videoreel (32 min., 49 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Tent revival, 8/2. Original ID # V-80-G-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV123, July 17, 1980, 1 videoreel (29 min., 30 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Revival, 9/3. Original ID # V-80-G-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV124, July 17, 1980, 1 videoreel (31 min., 14 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Revival, #4. Original ID # V-80-G-4.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV125, July 18, 1980, 1 videoreel (31 min., 57 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Tent revival, 11/1. Original ID # V-80-H-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV126, July 20, 1980, 1 videoreel (31 min., 50 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Tent revival, 12/1. Original ID # V-80-H-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV127, 1 videoreel (31 min., 43 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Rev. Roy Phillips and Rev. Isaih [sic] Tent revival, 13/3. Original ID # V-80-H-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV128, 1 videoreel (31 min., 5 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    14. Music at Cumberland Gap, Tennessee, 14; Road signs. Original ID # V-80-I-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV129, July 22, 1980, July 27, 1980, 1 videoreel (31 min., 46 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    15/1 Meeting in Middlesboro. Kentucky (July 22, 1980); Baptism (July 27, 1980). Original ID # V-80-J-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV130, July 27, 1980, 1 videoreel (29 min., 58 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Baptism, 16/2. Original ID # V-80-K-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV131, August 1, 1980, 1 videoreel (32 min., 53 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Tent revival, 17/1. Original ID # V-80-L-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV132, August 1, 1980, 1 videoreel (32 min., 40 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Tent revival, 18/2. Original ID # V-80-L-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV133, 1 videoreel (29 min., 44 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Tent revival; Rev. Roy Phillips, 19/3, 19/1. Original ID # V-80-L-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV134, August 2, 1980, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (22 min., 29 sec.): analog, sound, color; 3⁄4 in. (width)
    Tent revival, #1. Original ID # V-80-L-4.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV135, August 2, 1980, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (22 min.): analog, sound, color; 3⁄4 in. (width)
    Tent revival, #2. Original ID # V-80-L-5.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV136, August 2, 1980, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (22 min., 11 sec.): analog, sound, color; 3⁄4 in. (width)
    Tent revival, 22/#3. Original ID # V-80-L-6.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV137, August 2, 1980, 1 videocassette (U-matic) (22 min., 13 sec.): analog, sound, color; 3⁄4 in. (width)
    Tent revival, 23/#4. Original ID # V-80-L-7.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV138, 1 videoreel (31 min., 50 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Rev. Roy Phillips; Rev. Clay Ogle. Original ID # V-80-L-10.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV139, 1 videoreel (helical) (28 min., 48 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Dan White Show - interview, 26. Original ID # V-80-M-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV140, August 5, 1980, 1 videoreel (32 min., 37 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Tent revival, Pigeon Forge, Tenn. Original ID # V-80-N-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV141, August 6, 1980, 1 videoreel (32 min., 47 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Jean Schilling and Lee Schilling, 29/1. Original ID # V-80-O-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV142, 1 videoreel (30 min., 12 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Jean Schilling and Lee Schilling; Victory Temple Tent Revival, 30. Original ID # V-80-P-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV143, August 8, 1980, 1 videoreel (32 min., 7 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Tent Revival, 31/1. Original ID # V-80-P-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV144, August 1980, 1 videoreel (32 min., 33 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Tent Revival, 32/2. Original ID # V-80-P-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV145, 1 videoreel (33 min., 47 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Interviews after baptism; tent revival, 33/1. Original ID # V-80-Q-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV146, 1 videoreel (28 min., 50 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Tent Revival, 34/2. Original ID # V-80-Q-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV147, August 16, 1980, 1 videoreel (30 min., 40 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Kerosene Lantern; Lord's Supper and foot washing, #1. Original ID # V-80-R-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV148, August 16, 1980, 1 videoreel (33 min., 33 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Kerosene Lantern Revival Service, 36/2. Original ID # V-80-R-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV149, August 16, 1980, 1 videoreel (32 min., 16 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Kerosene Lantern Revival Service, #3. Original ID # V-80-R-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV150, August 16, 1980, 1 videoreel (32 min., 52 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Kerosene Lantern Revival, 38/4. Original ID # V-80-R-4.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV151, 1 videoreel (32 min., 20 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    New Light Missionary Baptist Church, 39. Original ID # V-80-S-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV152, June 1981, 1 videoreel (31 min., 44 sec.): analog, sound, black and white and color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Mattie Mae Lawson; Mrs. Roger Powell. Original ID # V-81-A.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV153, 1 videoreel (32 min., 8 sec.): analog, color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Irene Russell and car; Sister and Brother H.H. Mayes. Original ID # V-81-B.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV154, 1 videoreel (32 min., 52 sec.): analog, color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Rev. Roger Powell and car; Wayne Simmons. Original ID # V-81-C.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV155, July 22 1981, 1 videoreel (28 min., 54 sec.): analog, color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Tent revival. Original ID # V-81-D.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV156, 1 videoreel (32 min., 32 sec.): analog, sound, color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Dining on the grounds; Baptism creek; Irene Russell; Guilt, Rev. and Mrs. Roger Powell. Original ID # V-81-E.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV157, August 2, 1980, 1 videoreel (32 min., 38 sec.): analog, sound, color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Rev. Howard Finster, #1. Original ID # V-81-F-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV158, August 2, 1981, 1 videoreel (58 min., 26 sec.): analog, color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Rev. Howard Finster, #2. Original ID # V-81-F-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV159, August 2, 1981, 1 videoreel (32 min., 58 sec.): analog, sound, color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Rev. Howard Finster, 3/1; Elkmont. Original ID # V-81-F-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV160, 1 videoreel (32 min., 58 sec.): analog, color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Homecoming, #1. Original ID # V-81-H-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV161, 1 videoreel (33 min.): analog, sound, color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Homecoming, #2. Original ID # V-81-H-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV162, 1 videoreel (32 min., 46 sec.): analog, sound, color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Homecoming, #3. Original ID # V-81-H-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV163, 1 videoreel (32 min., 55 sec.): analog, sound, color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Serpent hunt. Original ID # V-81-I-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV164, 1 videoreel (22 min., 48 sec.): 4.5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Serpent boxes. Original ID # V-81-I-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV165, 1 videoreel: analog, color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Quilt; Rev. and Mrs. Powell. Original ID # V-81-J.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV166, August 19, 1981, 1 videoreel (31 min., 50 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Easter Sunday. No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV167, April 19, 1981, 1 videoreel (35 min., 40 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
  - AFC 1970/001: MV168, April 19, 1981, 1 videoreel (31 min., 14 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
  - AFC 1970/001: MV169, September 9, 1981-October 23, 1981, 1 videoreel (32 min., 50 sec.): analog, sound, color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
  - AFC 1970/001: MV170, April 11, 1981, 1 videoreel (32 min., 59 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Easter service. Original ID # V-82-A-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV171, April 11, 1981, 1 videoreel (32 min., 20 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Easter service. Original ID # V-82-A-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV172, April 11, 1981, 1 videoreel (30 min., 23 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Easter service. No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV173, August 23, 1982, 1 videoreel (28 min., 33 sec.): analog, sound, color; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Rev. Howard Finster and Brother H.H. Mayes. No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV174, April 3, 1983, 1 videoreel (33 min.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Easter Sunday service. No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV175, 1 videocassette (Betamax) (55 min., 22 sec.): 1⁄2 in. (width)